You dropped this.
你把这个掉了。
"part 1"
“第1部分”
Please include a nice ribbon.
请附上一条漂亮的丝带。
Let's put up a sign.
我们来立个牌子吧。
“Rooftop Movie Party with Lomocon”
“与 Lomocon 一起参加屋顶电影派对”
The right one is slightly higher.
右边稍微高一点。
Yes, I understand.
是的，我知道了。
So be it.
就这样吧。
Yes, I am Park Yoon-joo from PR JoA.
是的，我是 PR JoA 的朴允珠。
We rented 50 chairs , but they haven't all arrived yet.
我们租了50把椅子 ，但还没全部到。
- Manager - Can you send it to me now?
- 经理 - 你现在可以发给我吗？
Wait a minute, what's going on?
稍等一下，这是怎么回事？
Come check this one out.
快来看看这个吧。
About ten people are missing.
大约有十人失踪。
No one sent it?
没人送吗？
Let the first person come...
让第一个人来...
Uncle, go this way.
叔叔，这边走。
Wait, uncle, don't leave yet.
等等，叔叔，你先别走。
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
No
不
There are not enough chairs and no one delivers them.
椅子不够 没有人送。
Li Zhejiang, I don’t have time to chat now.
李哲酱， 我现在没时间闲聊。
There is definitely time.
肯定有时间。
Look, 90% of our guests canceled.
看，90% 的客人都取消了。
The chairs are more than adequate.
椅子绰绰有余。
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
An absolute disaster.
绝对是一场灾难。
A classic movie from the 90s? Definitely fits the retro theme.
90年代的经典电影？ 绝对符合复古主题。
If no one is born in the 1990s, what’s the point?
如果没有人是90后，那 还有什么意义呢？
Invite everyone you know. Li Zhe Zhang.
邀请所有你认识的人。李哲张。
Hey, look how nice the weather is.
嘿嘿，看看天气多好。
Do you think people will sleep at home?
你认为人们会在家睡觉吗？
But we should call everyone who can.
但我们应该给所有有能力的人打电话。
But why haven’t the new employees arrived yet?
可是新员工怎么还没有到呢？
A student at Seoul National High School?
首尔国立高中的学生？
I really do not understand.
我真的不明白。
Graduated from Seoul National University. Why do you want to work here?
毕业于首尔大学。为什么想在这里工作？
Is it so hard to find a job now?
现在工作这么难找吗？
What I don't understand is why can't I see her here now?
我不明白的是 为什么现在我在这里看不到她了？
Where is Mr. Shin Ji-hyo now?
申智孝先生现在在哪里？
- This - This is Jihyo.
- 这 - 这是志效。
Hello, please wait a moment.
你好，请稍等一下。
Hey, I told you. Asking for leave before starting work
嘿，我告诉过你了。 开始工作前请假
No, the president has agreed.
不，总统已经同意了。
So "Park Yoon-joo" is not "nee"?
那么“朴允珠”不是“nee”吗？
OMG.
我的天啊。
Thank you, Manager Park Yoon-joo.
谢谢朴允珠经理。
Do you want me to leave now?
你要我现在就走吗？
How many people can I bring?
我可以带多少人？
- Hello , welcome.
- 你好 ，欢迎。
- hello - here
- 在这里
- Nice to meet you. it's here. - One by one.
- 很高兴见到你。在这里。 - 一位一位。
I'll show you around, so just follow along.
我带你四处看看，跟着走吧。
Hello
你好
This is Lomocon...
这是洛莫康...
- Are you there yet? - We haven't seen each other for a long time.
- 你到了吗？ - 我们已经很久没见面了。
-This is food. -Okay , let's have a drink. Let's have a drink.
-这是食物。- 好吧，我们喝一杯吧。我们喝一杯吧。
Can't take pictures of me.
不能给我拍照。
Okay, I'll take pictures now.
好的，我现在就拍照。
Joe
乔
Seriously, why is it taking so long? I've been playing for hours.
说真的，为什么要花这么长时间？ 我已经打了好几个小时了。
She is crazy. Told me to close the bar so I could watch a movie.
她疯了。 叫我关掉酒吧，这样我就可以看电影了。
She has no customers anyway. until 10 p.m.
反正她没有顾客。 直到晚上 10 点
Hehe, the whole store is crowded with people.
嘿嘿，整个店里都挤满了人。
After the event I went to have dinner. In your bar?
活动结束后我去吃晚饭。 在你的酒吧吗？
Yes Yes.
是的是的。
But shouldn't she take it out?
但她不应该把它拿出来吗？
People born in the 90s?
90后的人？
Which
哪个
Why can't I have you and me?
为什么我不能拥有你和我？
We were born in 1990
我们出生于1990年
It's still the 90s.
现在还是90年代。
And one more thing...
还有一件事...
- Hello .
- 你好 你好。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
- let me see - we look really good
-让我想想 -我们看起来真的很好
"Yun Qiao's sister. Ten years old."
“允乔的妹妹。十岁”
We look good. Let's take some more photos.
我们看起来不错。我们多拍几张照片吧。
- Come on - Would you like to take a picture with me?
- 来吧 - 你愿意和我合影吗？
"Yoon Joo's mother, 50 years old"
“允珠的母亲，50岁”
“Yunjo is older than his first job, in his 50s.”
“Yunjo 比他第一份工作年长， 50 多岁。”
It's here and yes, more will be coming soon.
就在这里，是的，很快就会有更多的人来。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
“Customers over 40 years old”
“40岁以上的顾客”
"President of Joa Public Relations Company, 40 years old"
“Joa公关公司社长， 40岁”
- Yes - Are you sure?
- 是的 - 你确定吗？
certainly.
当然。
- That's... - This way.
- 那是... - 这边。
Yes
是的
I can't believe we were able to drag people out here. But none of them are in their 20s.
我不敢相信我们能够把人拖到这里。 但他们中没有一个是20多岁的人。
Hey, Li Zhejiang, let's do what we prepared.
嘿，李哲酱， 让我们做我们准备好的事情吧。
Last word challenge? Well, of course.
最后一句话挑战？好吧，当然。
Last word challenge?
最后一句话挑战？
"Challenge 'The Last Word' with Lomocon"
“与 Lomocon 一起挑战‘遗言’”
Post-90s
90后
This is a job suitable for young people in their 20s and early 30s.
这是一份适合20多岁和30岁出头的年轻人的工作。
We'll take pictures in front of the body along with the last words
我们将在尸体前拍照 连同最后的话
"I want to donate my property. Create a value of hundreds of billions for society."
“我想捐赠财产。 为社会创造价值千亿”
Can you send this? Look, Haejonie.
你能寄这个吗？看，Haejonie。
But there’s nothing sad or depressing about it at all.
但根本没有什么悲伤或沮丧的地方。
This is a lighthearted last word challenge.
这是一个轻松愉快的最后一句话挑战。
The key is that it has to be easy.
关键是它必须是轻松的。
Only those born in the 1990s can do this.
只有90后 才能做到这一点。
Hey, if you cry again I'll kill you.
嘿，你再哭我就杀了你。
I've had enough
我已经忍够了
"I've had enough, but here it comes again."
“我已经忍够了，但又来了。”
"Let's fall in love again in the next life. Men are the best."
“下辈子我们再相爱吧。 男人是最好的。”
Love is the best.
爱是最好的。
Gee, why does she look so stressed?
哎呀，她怎么看起来这么有压力啊？
That's it.
就是这样。
"Sorry, but I'm really dying."
“抱歉，但我真的快死了。”
"I'm so happy to have you in my life."
“我很高兴生命中有你们。”
What's this?
这是什么？
I want this photo.
我想要这张照片。
I really had to use photos of dead bodies.
我真的不得不使用尸体的照片。
Why are you talking about corpse pictures here?
你为什么在这里谈论尸体图片？
everyone
每个人
I'm happy because of them.
因为他们我很开心。
I often hang out with them.
我经常和他们一起出去玩。
Thanks.
谢谢。
- She was really crying. - What?
- 她真的哭了 - 什么？
- What's up with her? - she...
- 她怎么了？ - 她...
- I can't believe it. - What did you say?
- 我简直不敢相信 - 你说什么？
- What happened? - Why didn't you tell me right away?
- 发生了什么事？ - 你为什么不立即告诉我？
- Why? - what happened?
- 为什么？ - 发生了什么？
this
这
Things get really weird.
事情变得很奇怪。
Because I know what's going to happen
因为我知道事情会怎样
No, we are in this together. We will die together.
不，我们在一起。 我们会一起死去。
This isn't fair.
这不公平。
Here, step back.
这里，向后退。
Drink until you are completely drunk.
喝到完全醉为止。
- Pour it for me. - Please show me the way.
- 帮我倒一下 - 请给我指路
That!
那！
- here are our drinks - here
-这是我们的饮料 -这里
- There will be many things in life - Soju has arrived.
- 生活中会有很多事情 - 烧酒已经到来。
It's like glass.
它就像玻璃一样。
- Empty glass, fill it.
- 空玻璃杯，把它装满。
If the cup is empty, fill it.
如果杯子是空的，请将其装满。
uncle
叔叔
Turn the volume down a little. We are watching a movie together.
把音量调低一点。我们正在一起看电影。
- Noisy - What's wrong?
- 吵闹 - 怎么了？
- If you want a drink go to a bar - here
- 如果你想喝酒就去酒吧 - 这里
- Let's watch a movie. - What did you say?
- 我们看电影吧 - 你说什么？
- Shut up ...
- 闭嘴 ...
- Hey - stop.
- 嘿 - 停下来。
- What? - No.
- 什么？ - 不。
- I'm sorry - What did you say?
- 对不起 - 你说什么？
- Believe it or not - let the kid go.
- 不管你信不信 - 让孩子走吧。
This guy has no manners at all.
这小子一点礼貌都没有。
Hey, don't cry.
嘿，别哭。
There will be many things in life. Enjoy every moment until death is enough.
生活中会有很多事情。 享受每一刻，直到死亡就够了。
Damn it, be quiet.
该死的，安静点。
It's not just you.
不只是你们。
Let's watch movies together.
我们一起看电影。
I just found out today that my friend is dying
我今天才发现 我的朋友快要死了
Didn't you see we were watching a movie?
你没看到我们正在看电影吗？
- Sorry - Hey
- 对不起 - 嘿
- It's not just you here. - Let me watch the movie
- 这里不只是你们。 - 让我看电影吧
- I'm sorry - Damn it
- 对不起 - 该死的
Like countless photos in my memory
就像无数张照片一样 在我的记忆中
I know that as time goes by, love will eventually become a memory
我知道随着时间的流逝 爱情终将成为回忆
But you will never become a memory
但你永远不会成为回忆
Because of you, I can leave with the love in my heart.
因为有你，我才能带着心中的爱离开。
I want to thank you for this.
我想为此感谢你。
“#90s电影 #augustchristmas#moviemovie”
“#90 年代电影 #八月圣诞节#电影电影”
“#filmcamera#lastwordchallenge”
“#胶片相机#遗言挑战”
"#lastwordchallenge# was born in the 1990s"
“#遗言挑战#生于90年代”
Don't include "born in the 1990s" at all.
根本不要包括“90 年代出生”。
There are three of us, you, me and Li Zhezhang.
我们三个人， 你，我，李哲张。
But none of them are in their 20s, and that's the problem.
但他们都不是20多岁，这就是问题所在。
But it's still profound.
但它仍然是深刻的。
But you're not reassured, right?
但你并不放心，对吧？
not at all
一点也不
Should I change the name of the challenge?
我应该更改挑战的名称吗？
Not "last words of comfort" post-90s generation"
不是“安慰的遗言” 90后”
But are they “the true last words of all generations”?
但它们是“历代人真正的遗言”吗？
- Can you change it? - No, you can't change it.
- 你能改变它吗？ - 不，你不能改变它。
The customers are only from the post-90s generation.
顾客只来自90后。
Seriously, is this called a promotion?
说真的， 这也叫促销？
- Miss, I'm sorry - Oh my God.
- 小姐，对不起 - 天啊
No, don't stop me.
不，别阻止我。
- Back off - I won't stop you.
- 退后 - 我不会阻止你
- Needless to say
- 不用说 - 我不会阻止你。
- I didn't touch you at all - Damn, today...
-我根本没碰你 -该死，今天...
damn it.
该死的。
can you accept?
你能接受吗？
But I'm a fast bowler.
但我是一个速度很快的投手。
- Good throw - Wow.
- 扔得好 - 哇。
- Do you play baseball? - I'll ask.
- 你打棒球吗？ - 我会问。
- I want popcorn - Yes, I just made it this morning.
- 我要爆米花 - 是的，我今天早上刚做的。
- Why is it so delicious ? - Right?
- 为什么这么好吃 ？ - 对吧？
- For your next job... - Make delicious popcorn.
- 为了下一份工作... - 制作美味的爆米花。
The Seoul National University freshman turned off his phone. And in the end it didn't show up at all.
那个首尔大学的新生关掉了手机。 而最后却根本没有出现。
WHO？
WHO？
a child
一个孩子
Drink.
喝吧。
I don't even deserve a drink.
我什至不值得喝一杯。
Who said there would be a party? After finishing the work here
谁说会有聚会？ 在这里完成工作后
You have to drink.
你必须喝酒。
Yeah, I'll drink it all.
是的，我会把它全部喝掉。
very good
非常好
Damn it
该死
too delicious
太好吃了
Hey, why didn't Jimin come?
哎，杰珉怎么没来？
She also played his favorite movies.
她还播放了他最喜欢的电影。
He went camping.
他去露营了。
I've been seeing a lot of this lately.
最近，我看到了很多这样的事情。
Are you camping alone?
你一个人露营吗？
have no idea
不知道
Maybe he's hiding his girlfriend, who knows?
也许他隐藏了他的女朋友，谁知道呢？
I should live like Jaemin.
我应该像宰珉那样生活。
Don't they work in the same line of work? Have you met him?
他们不是在同一行工作吗？ 你见过他吗？
No, never once.
不，从来没有一次。
He works in the public relations department of a large company. Top of the food chain
他在一家大公司的公共关系部门工作。 食物链顶端
I work for a small company. bottom of food chain
我在一家小公司工作。 食物链底层
This is a brutally racist society.
这是一个残酷的种族主义社会。
Damn, there's so much going on, I want to drink it.
该死，发生了这么多事情，我想喝它。
This is too strong. Give me some soju.
这太烈了。给我一些烧酒吧。
- This would be better, right? - oh.
- 这样会更好，对吧？ - 哦。
here it is.
这里是。
"Cui Huiying"
“崔慧英”
Who is this ? My favorite reporter Choi.
这是谁 ？我最喜欢的崔记者。
very happy
非常开心
where
哪里
I'm not in Seoul.
我不在首尔。
Good night
晚安
"Daguo Daily"
《大国日报》
I'm sending a file. Open it now and take a look.
我正在发送文件。 现在打开看看。
"Cui Huiying"
“崔慧英”
Changing the manufacturer of Seyon in "Choi Hye Young: Bribery Auction" ? "
《崔惠英：贿赂拍卖会》 更换Seyon的制造商？”
"Bribery auction to replace Seyon's manufacturer?"
“贿赂拍卖会
"Read all"
“阅读全部”
"Bribery auction to replace Seyon's manufacturer?"
更换Seyon的制造商？”
"Company A comes in as a producer. Not Company B..."
“A公司作为制片人进来。 而不是B公司……”
"I suspect bribery. Change the manufacturer to Company A"
“我怀疑有贿赂行为。 将制造商更改为A公司”
- In the paper on Monday morning? - very happy.
- 周一早上在报纸上？ - 很高兴。
Author: Senior Majalak
作者：高级马贾拉克
Do you think you can turn off the news?
你觉得你可以关掉新闻吗？
It's up to you, isn't it?
这取决于你，不是吗？
If you can't, I'll pretend you didn't call me.
如果你不能， 我会假装你没有给我打电话。
At least I can enjoy the weekend.
至少我可以享受周末。
- Didn't you cry when you saw the coffin? - Can you turn off the news?
- 你看到棺材的时候没有流泪吗？ - 你能关掉新闻吗？
Check out my post. He knew that we graduated from the same university.
看看我发布的消息。 他知道我们是同一所大学毕业的。
- That means you want us to cover up the news - You're addicted to alcohol
- 这意味着你希望我们掩盖这个消息 - 你酗酒成瘾
Come on, bug manager.
快点，错误经理。
Manager Meng, please answer the phone quickly.
孟经理，你快点接电话吧。
Did you get drunk a little too quickly?
你是不是喝醉的有点太快了？
Hey Brother Zhejun, I just sent you the file.
嘿哲俊哥，我刚刚把文件发给你了。
I think you should tell your boss first.
我觉得你应该先告诉老板。
I...I just got home...
我……我刚回到家……
- Go to sleep, go to sleep - I'm dizzy...
- 快睡吧，快睡吧 - 我头晕……
Yes
是的
- Oh - Go home and sleep.
- 哦 - 回家睡觉吧。
Stop sleeping on the side of the road. You'll freeze to death in no time.
别再睡在路边了。 你很快就会冻死。
" Song Sun-tae, Director of Publicity Department 2 of Shiyong Strategic Management Department"
“世勇战略管理部 宣传2部部长宋善泰”
- Boss - Uh.
- 老板 - 呃。
Oh, why are you here alone?
哦，你怎么一个人来了？
Where is Zhejun?
哲俊呢？
He is not in good health.
他身体不太好。
You bastard!
你这个混蛋！
A reporter from Daguo Daily came to Zaile?
大国日报记者来到宰乐？
Yes
是的
I've never heard of this name before.
我以前从未听说过这个名字。
who told you that?
谁告诉你？
Reporter Choi Hye-young graduated from the same university
记者 崔惠英 同一所大学毕业
Yes, Director Zhang.
是的，张主任。
Oh, sorry to bother you so early in the morning.
噢，抱歉这么一大早打扰你。
I won't bother you if it's not necessary.
如果没有必要，我不会打扰你。
How is this going? What happened to the reporter?
这是怎么回事？记者怎么了？
He had me running around. It's the weekend.
他让我到处乱跑。 现在是周末。
Ah right?
啊对？
I think he's a little too enthusiastic.
我觉得他有点太热情了。
That said, we will check the facts.
也就是说，我们将核实事实。
But Monday is too early, right?
但星期一还太早了，对吧？
oh!
哦！
I didn't ask you to stop posting about this.
我没有问你 不要再发布有关此事的新闻了。
You have to find out the facts. and listen to some stories around us
你必须找出事实。 并听听我们身边的一些故事
Yes, yes, golf sounds good.
是的，是的，高尔夫听起来不错。
Was the previous session good? I will make an appointment and call you back.
之前的场不错吧？ 我会预约并给您回电话。
Yes Yes.
是的是的。
this afternoon
今天下午
Go find a reporter.
去找记者吧。
Go find out what that bastard wants.
去看看那个混蛋想要什么。
I made a lot of phone calls. Both parties send messages
我打了很多电话。 双方都发送消息
But he didn't answer at all.
但他根本没有回答。
He seemed to be avoiding me.
他好像在躲避我。
He really wanted to talk to this big guy.
他真的很想和这个大家伙谈谈。
I'll keep calling.
我会继续打电话。
"Corruption is still rampant"?
“腐败依然猖獗”？
"Corruption is still rampant. Is it in the company?"
“腐败现象依然猖獗。 是在公司里吗？”
Its purpose is to use a negative word.
它的目的是使用一个否定词。
Damn that bastard.
该死的，这个混蛋。
He should have arrived.
他应该已经到了。
You are here.
你在这。
"Siyong Sales Department, Sales Team 1, Team Leader Zhao Zhenrui"
“四勇营业部，营业一队， 组长赵镇瑞”
Senior Song
高级宋
What exactly is this?
这到底是什么？
There are no problems at the Changwon factory.
昌原工厂没有任何问题。
Who is the manager there? He was interviewed here.
那里的经理是谁？ 他在这里接受了采访。
I have read this article. He didn't say much.
我读过这篇文章。 他没有多说什么。
It doesn't work anymore. Go see the factory director.
它不再起作用了。 你去见厂长吧。
Have you gone to Changwon?
你去昌原了吗？
“364 kilometers in 4 hours and 50 minutes”
“4小时50分钟364公里”
Yes
是的
Why
为什么
No.
不。
But if I were living in Changwon and reporters came...
但如果我住在昌原 当记者赶来时...
Why don't you answer the phone?
为什么说不接电话？
If he accepts, do I have to fly back to Seoul?
如果他接受，我是否必须飞回首尔？
Yes
是的
Any questions? Don't you understand what I'm saying?
有什么问题吗？你不明白我在说什么吗？
No, I'm going there now.
不，我现在就去那儿。
Hey, tell Cheol-joon you don't have to come back to work.
嘿，告诉哲俊 你不必回来工作。
that lazy bastard
那个懒惰的混蛋
Senior, this is Tai Chi Daily. Is there anything you want from us?
前辈，这里是《太极日报》。 您想从我们这里得到什么吗？
correct?
正确的？
"Manager Zhejun"
《哲俊经理》
Man, he kicked you out.
兄弟，他把你赶出去了。
Will this make me avoid them?
这会让我避开他们吗？
"Changwon Factory"
《昌原工厂》
I did not mean that.
我不是那个意思。
I'm just asking you to call. First, our PR department
我只是请你打电话。 首先是我们的公关部门
When the media comes and asks for an interview , instead of answering it yourself
当媒体前来要求采访时 而不是自己回答
But I didn't say anything bad.
但我并没有说任何不好的话。
I'm not talking about using power. in the wrong way
我不是在谈论使用权力。 以错误的方式
I told you this was a normal interview.
我告诉过你 这是一次正常的采访。
They may lie to you. There are a lot of questions, and that’s great.
他们可能会欺骗你。 有很多问题，那很好。
We just want to be more careful.
我们只是想更加小心。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
Sigh, let me die.
叹息，让我死吧。
And where does it say that the news hasn’t spread yet?
而且哪里说消息还没有传出来？
You're in the public relations department. Can't stop them?
你在公共关系部。 无法阻止他们吗？
It's your duty to prevent this, isn't it?
你有责任阻止这种事情， 不是吗？
Yes, that's why I'm here.
是的，这就是我来这里的原因。
I have to understand the situation. You can stop the news coverage.
我必须了解情况。 你可以停止新闻报道。
I didn't say anything I shouldn't have said.
我没有说任何不该说的话。
"Angus Bread"
《安格斯面包》
"bread"
“面包”
A cocoa flavor, a cocoa protein cake.
一种可可口味， 一种可可蛋白蛋糕。
a protein cake
一份蛋白蛋糕
Do you eat here?
你在这里吃饭吗？
Please give me a protein bar.
请给我一根蛋白质棒。
- One of each - Take everything away
- 各一份 - 把所有东西都拿走
- Good Luck - Thank you Goodbye
- 祝你好运 - 谢谢你 再见
- Hello
- 你好
welcome.
欢迎。
Work hard and you will die.
努力工作，你就会死。
That's what I said.
我是这么说的。
Having said that, you have to thank me for the challenge.
话虽如此，你必须感谢我的挑战。
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Changwon Factory
昌原工厂
Let's turn off the news. And you?
我们关掉新闻吧。你呢？
Come find new clients.
快来寻找新客户吧。
There is a store I have been keeping an eye on. It's been a few months now.
有一家店我一直在关注。 现在已经过去几个月了。
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
You shouldn't work on holidays.
你不应该在假期工作。
You work here too.
你也在这里工作。
Because I have to but she doesn't have to.
因为我必须 但她不必这样做。
It's very different.
这是非常不同的。
You never make a mistake. But I've also made mistakes.
你从来没有犯过错误。 但我也犯过错误。
Eat here or take home.
在这里吃饭或带回家。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
"Last Call"
“最后一次通话”
"Call Majae Rak, reporter of "Daguo Daily"."
“致电 《大国日报》记者 Majae Rak。”
Not accepted.
不接受。
If you accept, I will kill you.
如果你接受，我就杀了你。
Honestly, don't accept it.
说实话，不要接受。
I told you not to accept it.
我告诉过你不要接受。
If you don’t accept it, please don’t accept it.
不接受，请不要接受。
The number you dialed cannot be contacted. Please leave a message...
无法联系您拨打的号码。 请留言...
Yes
是的
It was a call from Seyong's public relations department.
是 Seyong 公关部门打来的电话。
I've requested that access to the news be blocked, but...
我已经要求阻止访问新闻， 但是...
You will be asked to attend an interview. Advance reservations are not possible.
您将被要求参加面试。 无法提前预约。
We only handle auctions.
我们只负责拍卖。
Everything after that will be taken care of by the company.
之后的一切，公司都会处理。
There is no way to plan for something like this. Put it first.
没有办法计划这样的事情。 把它放在第一位。
"Manual of Drug Advertising Regulations"
《药品广告管理规定手册》
If it had happened I would have told you.
如果真的发生了 我早就告诉过你了。
Reporter O
记者O
- It's not true, I told you. - Is this the guy I talked to before?
- 这不是真的，我告诉过你了 - 是我之前聊过的那个人吗？
That article is not true.
那篇文章不属实。
- still looking - of course
-仍在寻找 -当然
- Why do you say they were all deleted? - We are paying close attention.
- 你为什么说全部被删除了？ - 我们正在密切关注。
We will make a statement. It will be officially released soon.
我们将发表声明。 很快就会正式发布。
When will Assistant Ryu be ready?
Ryu助理什么时候能准备好？
- Seyong Public Relations - Five minutes.
- Seyong 公共关系部 - 五分钟。
Five minutes to go.
还有五分钟。
If you wait a little longer...
如果再等一会儿的话...
Hello
你好
"Shi Yong, Media and Public Relations Department 2. "
“世勇，媒体公关二部 。”
damn it.
该死的。
- Mr. Seung Hee - Yes.
- Seung Hee 先生 - 是的。
Are you sure all news has been deleted?
你确定所有新闻都被删除了吗？
I'll check again.
我会再检查一下。
So you left?
所以你走了？
Things don't look good at all.
情况看上去一点也不妙。
They can't turn off the news.
他们无法关闭新闻。
Why is it so smooth?
为什么它这么流畅？
- Yes, Reporter Park - We lost contact during the game yesterday.
- 是的，朴记者 - 昨天我们在比赛时失去了联系。
Also please turn off your mobile phone.
另外请关闭手机。
Well, it's the weekend.
嗯，现在是周末。
Hey, man, look at his bag. Have a resignation letter.
嘿，伙计，看看他的包。 有一封辞职信。
What he said in that interview is not true...
他在那次采访中说的话 这不是真的...
Hey, they fired me because I couldn't work on the holidays.
嘿，他们解雇了我， 因为我不能在假期工作。
This is against labor laws.
这是违反劳动法的。
Anyway
反正
I thought they solved this problem with seminar tickets. This is from the president of Daguo Daily.
我以为他们用研讨会门票解决了这个问题。 这是大国日报社长发来的。
I might want more.
我可能想要更多。
Isn’t that 4 million won per ticket?
那不是每张票400万韩元吗？
Hey, those slimy reporters.
嘿，那些黏糊糊的记者。
Yes, I'm listening. bring it on.
是的，我在听。来吧。
Probably around noon.
大概是中午左右吧。
We will send you a statement. As for other questions...
我们将向您发送一份声明。 至于其他问题...
- I heard you went to Changwon - Yes
- 我听说你去了昌原 - 是的
What did the factory director say? Is it during the interview?
厂长说什么？ 是面试的时候吗？
That doesn't seem to be the case.
似乎并非如此。
So what does it look like?
那么它是什么样的呢？
Protein ingredient manufacturers have changed.
蛋白质原料生产商发生了变化。
But like previous manufacturers, they will provide false information to reporters.
但和之前的厂家一样 会向记者提供虚假信息
Very original script
非常原创的剧本
I slept with my ex-wife, what should I do?
我和前妻睡了，我该怎么办？
Ha, this idiot.
哈，这个白痴。
You are the manager.
你是经理。
can you hear me? Speak softly.
你能听到我说话吗？轻声说话。
I heard it all.
我都听到了。
sorry.
对不起。
I don't like you at all.
我一点也不喜欢你。
Yoo Jae-min
柳在民
Is the statement ready?
声明准备好了吗？
Yes, I'll give it to you now.
是的，我现在就给你。
hurry up.
快点。
It's about the new kids.
这是关于新来的孩子。
Have you been missing since Saturday?
你从星期六起就失踪了吗？
Didn't you call back at all?
你根本就没有回电话吗？
Yes
是的
To this day, he still hasn't called.
直到今天，他仍然没有打来电话。
Obviously, I don't want to work here.
显然，我不想在这里工作。
But it's impossible to go on like this, isn't it?
但这样下去是不可能的，不是吗？
Just a rude kid
只是一个没有礼貌的孩子
I already know that it won't be long before it all ends here.
我已经知道，不会太久 ，一切都会在这里结束。
I hope students can graduate from Seoul National University. You can't come to work in a place like this.
我希望学生们能够从首尔大学毕业。 不能来这样的地方上班。
This is Li Zhenjiang.
这是李振江。
It doesn't sound right.
听起来不对。
Why do you need to mention your university?
为什么一定要提到你的大学？
So is there anything bad here? why?
那么这里有什么不好的地方吗？为什么呢？
No, it's okay, I'm just saying.
不，没关系，我只是说说而已。
Not working
不工作
What makes you think that? This time, she'll answer the phone.
是什么让你这么想？ 这一次，她会接电话。
Please leave a message after the beep. Then press the star or square button
请在“嘟”声后留言。 然后按星号或方形按钮
Mr. Shin Ji Hyo, I am Park Yoon Jo from PR JoA.
申智孝先生，我是 PR JoA的Park Yoon Jo。
You never called me back.
你从来没有给我回电话。
As far as I know, this is how you announced your resignation.
据我所知， 这就是您宣布辞职的方式。
But work is not fun.
但工作并不好玩。
if you want to resign
如果你想辞职
Learn to be polite and put people in perspective.
学会有礼貌并让人们正确认识。
You are of the same generation. My reputation is completely ruined.
你们是同一代人。 我的名声已经彻底毁了。
That last sentence is pretty cool.
最后一句话非常酷。
"Shin Ji Hyo"
《申智孝》
What's wrong?
有什么不对？
It's okay, don't worry.
没关系，放心吧。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Those two people...
那两个人...
- Mr. Shin Ji-hyo... - Let me start.
- 申智孝先生... - 让我先说。
I have informed the President that I am on leave.
我已经通知总统我正在休假。
I never disobeyed you for a moment.
我一刻也没有违背你的意思。
So why don't you answer the phone?
那么你为什么不接电话呢？
You can leave a message here.
您可以在这里留言。
I have the right not to answer the phone. This has to do with holiday work.
我有权不接听电话。 这与假期工作有关。
Mr. Shin Ji-hyo
申智孝先生
As you can see, this is not a large company. We can never have enough people.
正如你所看到的，这不是一家大公司。 我们永远没有足够的人。
And you know deep down that we're going to be hosting the event on the weekend
你心里也知道 我们将在周末举办该活动
And your job is to take care of the guests.
而你的工作就是照顾客人。
You keep saying the same thing over and over again.
你总是一遍又一遍地说同样的话。
I have informed the president. I got off work that day
我已经通知总统了。 那天我下班了
You are not interested here.
你对这里不感兴趣。
Don't talk to me in that tone.
别用那种语气跟我说话。
I'm still your boss.
我还是你的老板。
Why did you act so unreasonably?
你为何做出如此无理的举动？
Or maybe it's because...
又或者是因为...
This is a small company. So you have no common sense.
这是一家小公司。 所以你没有常识。
not flexible...
不，灵活...
This is a benefit. of this small company.
这是一种福利。 这家小公司的。
unlike big companies
不像大公司
If not, what's the point of continuing to work here?
如果没有， 我继续在这里工作还有什么意义？
Work-life balance And the pay isn't great either.
工作与生活的平衡 而且工资也不好。
- Then you don't have to do it. - I definitely won't.
- 那你就不用这么做了 - 我绝对不会
Why am I resigning from today?
从今天起我怎么辞职了？
Mr. Shin Ji-hyo
申智孝先生
Sorry I forgot to tell...
抱歉我忘了告诉...
Manager Park and Lee Chul-jung, please explain that you are on vacation.
朴经理和李哲正 说明你正在休假。
Yes
是的
Yes, it is...
对，是...
If you say you want to resign, I won't back down.
你说你要辞职 我不会退缩。
But it's about balancing life with work and salary.
但这是为了平衡生活与工作 和薪水。
If you don't like anything else, you can tell me.
如果你不喜欢别的，可以告诉我。
I thought...
我本来以为...
Looking for a way to grow...
寻找发展之路...
My future small company
我未来的小公司
Do you really want to hear it?
你真的想听吗？
Yes
是的
I believe in having talented employees. This is even more important for small companies.
我相信拥有才华横溢的员工。 对于小公司来说更重要。
You should hire better people. Your company will be able to compete with other companies.
你应该雇用更好的人。 您的公司将能够与其他公司竞争。
What’s the point of working all night?
通宵工作有什么意义？
You don't have enough people to do it. Even a viral marketing project.
你没有足够的人来做这件事。 甚至是病毒式营销项目。
The efficiency is too low
效率太低了
This is a human resources issue.
这是人力资源的问题。
Moreover, there are only a few employees here.
而且， 这里的员工也只有几个。
Let’s just call each other cool. That'll be fun.
我们就这样互相称呼对方冷静吧。 那会很有趣的。
In fact, her name is Li Zhejiang.
其实她的名字叫李哲江。
Have been working here for a week. Don't you know about this?
已经在这里工作一周了。 难道你不知道这件事吗？
This is just a small company.
这只是一家小公司。
As far as I can see
据我所见
Manager Park and Lee Cheol Jung are both good.
朴经理和李哲正都不错。
Do you think so?
你这样认为吗？
Well, everyone has different standards.
嗯，每个人都有不同的标准。
Mr. Shin Ji-hyo thinks what makes employees...
申智孝先生认为 是什么让员工...
You are a talented person.
你是一个有才华的人。
I don't know anything else.
我不知道其他事情。
But probably not someone I don’t know. Balance life and work
但可能不是我不认识的人。 平衡生活和工作
Work-life balance This is a personal value.
工作与生活的平衡 这是一种个人价值。
This is not something that can be used to measure ability.
这不是可以用来衡量能力的东西。
I'm only giving my opinion because you asked.
我只是因为你问了才发表我的看法。
I will not discuss or argue with you.
我不会与你讨论或争论。
Mr. Shin Ji-hyo
申智孝先生
Can I still leave?
我还可以走吗？
I bet my life she finds a job somewhere else
我赌我的生命 她在其他地方找到了工作
You don't have to do this.
你不必这样做。
Really, I don't want to believe it.
真的，我不愿意相信。
“Party on the Lomocon Rooftop”
“Lomocon 屋顶上的派对”
What's wrong with today's children?
现在的孩子都怎么了？
- Do you understand them? - Are you a monk or something?
- 你明白它们吗？ - 你是和尚还是什么？
"Corporation: Conservatives"
“公司：保守派”
who I am?
我是谁？
wait for me?
等我？
Everything the child said was right.
孩子说的都对。
She thought she had informed the president. Isn't this okay?
她以为她已经通知了总统。 这样不行吗？
The girl turned off her phone. Do your job for me.
那个女孩关掉了手机。为我做你的工作。
Who asks for leave? Start with the first week of your new job.
谁请假？ 从新工作的第一周开始。
Can't you?
你不能吗？
you can not.
你不能。
You might not know this because I've never worked in a company.
你可能不知道 因为我从来没有在公司工作过。
But it can't do that.
但它不能那样做。
If there is an emergency, you can take a day off. What's the big deal?
如果有紧急事情，可以请一天假。 有什么大不了的？
Quiet.
安静。
OK
好的。
You know what?
你知道什么吗？
I will win this upcoming project.
我将赢得这个即将进行的项目。
That girl gave me fire. and feel like winning
那个女孩给了我火。 并有获胜的感觉
She looks down on me.
她看不起我。
I understand what you want to drink.
我明白你想喝什么。
This is a billion dollar project. Serong Cosmetics
这是一个耗资十亿美元的项目。 世容化妆品的
- Seyong - What are you drinking?
- Seyong - 你喝什么？
What is no padding?
什么是不填充？
I just do whatever needs to be done. He put it on the news anyway.
我只是做任何需要做的事。 无论如何，他还是将其发布在新闻上。
He did not break the news. So we can turn off the news
他没有发布这个消息。 这样我们就可以关闭新闻
He wanted to talk to someone at boss level.
他想和老板级别的人谈谈。
How does he know prices will rise again?
他怎么知道价格会再次上涨？
bad
糟糕的
What do we need in a moment like this?
在这样的时刻我们需要什么？
- Alcohol? - That's right.
- 酒精？ - 没错。
Tan Tan
但谭
"Utopia"
“乌托邦”
- "Tho"? - Cool name, right?
- “Tho”？ - 很酷的名字，对吧？
a while.
一会儿。
Oh, I was totally shocked.
哦，我完全震惊了。
Put my head back in place.
把我的头放回原位。
able
能
five degrees to the left
向左五度
left...
左边...
OK
好的
damn it.
该死的。
I was completely shocked.
我完全震惊了。
same
相同
Are you shocked?
你震惊吗？
Damn it
该死
Oh, indeed.
哦，确实如此。
this
这
welcome
欢迎
Hello
你好
Please sit here.
请坐在这里。
- thank you - right here
- 谢谢 - 就在这里
All three of them are in primary school. Or the same middle school?
他们三个都在上小学。 还是同一所中学？
- Yes Yes.
- 是的 是的。
I'm tired of them.
我厌倦了他们。
Reporter Choi graduated from college. Is it the same as Jaemin?
崔记者大学毕业。 是不是和渽民一样呢？
Your academic performance must be very good.
学习成绩一定很好。
not at all.
一点也不。
Actually we were just chatting. Your college junior will go on his own.
其实我们只是闲聊而已。 你的大学三年级学生会自己去。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
They are all children these days
这年头都是孩子了
I see.
我明白。
I see new employees at work who are in their early 20s.
我在工作中看到 20 岁出头的新员工。
I thought: "I've never been like this."
我想： “我从来没有这样过。”
Is it right?
是对的吗？
The worst thing is they don't answer the phone.
最糟糕的是他们不接电话。
that's right.
这是正确的。
Never picked up the phone.
从来没有接过电话。
Some people just send messages. Don't answer the phone either.
有些人只是发消息。 也不接电话。
Did you hear it?
你听到了吗？
I just called someone.
我刚刚打电话给某人。
- Very important thing - Yes.
- 非常重要的事情 - 是的。
But she kept messaging me. Don't answer my calls at all.
但她一直给我发信息。 根本不接我的电话。
- Do you get me? - What nonsense.
- 你明白我的意思吗？ - 真是胡说八道。
Hey, go away.
嘿，走开。
- Ha - What next?
- 哈 - 接下来呢？
- Why... - So I...
- 为什么... - 所以我...
- Change place? - Yes.
- 换地方？ - 是的。
- There's a typhoon coming now, right?
- 现在有台风来袭，对吗？
- You should answer the phone. The matter is urgent - yes.
- 你应该接电话。事情很紧急 ——没错。
She doesn't answer my calls. continue sending messages
她不接我的电话。继续发送消息
Damn it, why are you doing this?
该死，你为什么要这么做？
- Hey, you understand... - Yeah.
- 嘿，你明白吗... - 是的。
Yes, can you give me your business card?
是的，可以给我你的名片吗？
Can you give me your business card?
能给我您的名片吗？
"Open test consent form and restore safety"
“打开测试同意书 恢复安全”
OK, everything is ready.
好的，一切就绪。
What's this?
这是什么？
free.
免费。
Looks better than the real product.
看起来比真正的产品更好。
That's the beauty of free stuff.
这就是免费东西的美妙之处。
It's irresistible.
这是不可抗拒的。
This is real.
这是真的。
Of course, I'm always right.
当然，我总是对的。
Yes Yes.
是的是的。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Miss Huajia
华佳小姐
Why didn't I go to a regular high school?
为什么我没有读普通高中？
What the hell are you talking about?
你他妈在说什么？
Mr. Huazi won't let me study, will he?
华子先生不会让我学习吧？
He said he wanted me to make money. Immediately after high school graduation
他说他想让我赚钱。 高中毕业后立即
He went to study for a vocational certificate because he wanted to work immediately.
他去学习职业证书是因为他想立即工作。
Why do you blame me?
你为什么怪我？
- I? - Yes, that's you.
- 我？ - 是的，就是你。
At that time, Uncle Byung-gil had just been diagnosed with cancer.
那时的秉吉叔叔 刚刚诊断出患有癌症。
we need money
我们需要钱
You see, you chose it yourself.
你看，你自己选的。
The elevator is rising.
电梯正在上升。
I wouldn't be surprised if the elevator fell down now.
如果电梯现在掉下来，我不会感到惊讶。
No one is forcing us to move to this dilapidated building.
没有人强迫 我们搬到这座破旧的大楼去吧。
He is about to develop a new product here.
他即将在这里开发一款新产品。
We are leasing him.
我们正在租用他。
Even if you create a new one it's none of our business.
即使你创建了一个新的 这根本不关我们的事。
The deposit is so cheap.
押金这么便宜。
I didn't think about this at all.
我根本没想过这个。
I'm the one who paid the deposit.
我是付押金的人。
So why are you talking about high school?
那么你为什么要谈论高中呢？
It ended a long time ago.
很久以前就结束了。
there is nothing
没有什么
I just want to know if I studied in an ordinary high school...
就想知道我是不是在普通高中读的...
Would my life be different than it is now?
我的生活会和现在有所不同吗？
Why is life now?
人生为何是现在？
This is good.
这很好。
But I keep getting asked.
但我不断被问到。
It's very annoying.
它很烦人。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
Don't be too vague.
别搞得含糊不清。
Obviously, I'm not a smart person.
显然，我不是一个聪明的人。
Did the president speak?
总统讲话了吗？
No, that's not right.
不，这不对。
Speech by new employee who resigned
辞职新员工发言
What would she know?
她会知道什么？
that's right.
这是正确的。
She may look down on you. Because you can graduate from college online.
她可能看不起你。 因为您可以在线大学毕业。
Is it you Huajia?
是你华佳吗？
alright.
好啦好啦。
Isn't it?
不是吗？
Is it right?
是对的吗？
But talking about online college
但谈论在线大学
I didn’t even get a student loan.
我什至没有获得学生贷款。
I work to make money for myself.
我工作是为了自己赚钱。
Since working in accounting until now I started working in public relations.
自从从事会计工作以来 直到现在我开始从事公共关系工作。
Do you think it's easy?
你认为这很容易吗？
I changed jobs when I was 20 years old.
我20岁时换了工作。
real
真的
I don’t know how many 20-year-olds there are. Who doesn’t know what they want to do.
我不知道有多少20岁的人。 谁不知道自己想做什么。
What you do is amazing.
你所做的事情太棒了。
I work hard too.
我也很努力。
So why is my life so miserable?
那么为什么我的生活如此悲惨呢？
I only have my daughter to support me.
我只有女儿供养我。
Use your own money to pay the deposit.
拿你自己的钱 快来交房押金吧。
Only 30 million won.
才3000万韩元。
that is because...
那是因为...
Mr. Huajia always spends his money on stupid things.
华贾先生总是把钱花在愚蠢的事情上。
Hey, I spend my money on the people I love and the people I love.
嘿，我把钱花 在我爱的人和我爱的人身上。
Where is the waste?
浪费在哪里了？
Damn it
该死
A man?
一个男人？
Men are different.
男人则不同。
This is my life my man
这就是我的生活 我的男人
This is my cup, I bought it.
这是我的杯子，我买的。
How narrow-minded.
真是心胸狭隘。
Just a glass of soju
只需一杯烧酒
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
Is that me?
那是我吗？
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
Do you mean starting a company?
你是说开公司吗？
The manager is responsible.
经理负责。
Yes, usually the manager is responsible
是的，通常是经理 应该对此负责
But he seems very busy lately.
但最近他似乎很忙。
So I helped lighten the load for him.
所以我帮他减轻了负担。
Or you might have to take all the work away from him.
或者你可能不得不把所有的工作从他身上夺走。
If he was going to do anything he wouldn't let it go.
如果他打算做任何事 他不会放手的。
When you piss him off, it's all over.
当你惹他生气的时候，一切就都结束了。
Why does he have to be like this?
为什么他一定要这样？
Calm down and come back. Let us take responsibility for this again.
冷静下来然后回来。 让我们再次为此承担责任。
I was overloaded with work just now.
刚才我的工作超负荷了。
You know, if I don't get promoted, I have to quit.
你知道，如果我不再升职， 我就必须辞职。
Because of this, I should take my job back.
正因为如此，我应该收回我的工作。
You have to do something. To be evaluated
你必须做点什么。 待评估
Except drinking with reporters.
除了和记者喝酒。
So what went wrong?
那么出了什么问题呢？
That’s what PR people do.
公关人员就是这样做的。
It's work.
是工作。
Times have changed.
时代变了。
- Only the manager doesn't know - Yeah, I don't know
- 只有经理不知道 - 是的，我不知道
I don't want to know anything anymore.
我不想再知道任何事情了。
Oh, Chief Elf.
哦，首席精灵。
a while.
一会儿。
This is Director G.
这是G局长。
Is today’s digital world safe?
今天的数字世界安全吗？
shut your mouth
闭上你的嘴
Crazy cool
疯狂酷
We started working here together.
我们一起开始在这里工作。
But she became the head of the department. Be a team leader
但她却成为了部门主管。 成为团队领导者
Knowing this, I should probably go to the digital department.
知道这一点，我可能应该去数字部门。
Who drinks with reporters these days?
现在谁跟记者喝酒？
Hey, you old-school PR guy.
嘿，你这个老派的公关人员。
This is the information provided for bidding on this work. Is it cosmetics?
这是为该作品投标而提供的信息。 是化妆品吗？
It says "Auction" but the winner has already been chosen.
上面写着“拍卖”， 但获胜者已经选定。
You know who this is.
你知道这是谁。
Earth communication?
地球通讯？
Yes
是的
"PR Joea"
“公关乔阿”
It won't be like a regular cosmetics ad
它不会像 一般化妆品广告
while still conveying the essence
同时仍传达本质
This would be a clever advertisement. people can visit
这将是一个巧妙的广告。人们可以访问
We plan to invite influencers. Focus on beauty influencers
我们计划邀请有影响力的人。 专注于美容影响者
Go to publicity jobs and do various challenges in order to attract users...
去宣传工作和做各种挑战 为了吸引用户...
how
如何
I don't think it's necessary to come here.
我不认为有必要来这里。
A cup of original latte A cup of sweet latte
一杯原味拿铁 一杯甜拿铁
- Have an iced Americano - American...
- 喝一杯冰美式咖啡 - 美国...
- Sigh - But what happened?
- 叹息 - 但怎么了？
Sane's introduction?
萨恩的介绍？
do you know?
你知道吗？
I think she still doesn't know. But I work there.
我想她还是不知道。 但我在那里工作。
There is also a public relations department
还有公关部
Guess who does the demo?
猜猜谁负责演示？
you?
你？
So can I use some wire? Choose mine.
那我可以用一些电线吗？ 选择我的。
Oh, this depends on strength. The level of deputy manager is too high
哦，这就是看实力。 副经理的等级太高了
Come, please give me a glass of sweet wine. I need to add some sugar.
来，请给我一杯甜酒。 我需要加点糖。
Thanks
谢谢
Alas, if only I had been so diligent in high school.
唉，如果我高中时也这么勤奋就好了。
Maybe got into Harvard.
可能考上了哈佛。
Maybe I should...
也许我应该...
It actually says "auction."
它实际上说的是“拍卖”。
But the winner has already been chosen.
但获胜者已经选定。
- Earth communications? - Yes.
- 地球通信？ - 是的。
They want to be first in the industry.
他们希望成为行业第一。
Do you still accept people?
你还接受人吗？
Other PR Agencies Don’t you know this?
其他公关公司 你不知道这个吗？
You must not know.
你一定不知道。
That's all? Boss Song is here again.
就这样了？宋老板又来了。
Damn, it’s been ten years. But he still didn't let go.
妈的，已经十年了。 但他依然没有放手。
That evil Boss Song!
那个邪恶的宋老大！
"List of companies participating in the auction"
《参加拍卖的企业名单》
"Earth Communication Seo Dong-hoon Hello Hope Park Ji-young"
《地球通讯徐东勋你好希望 朴智英》
“PR Joa Kim Hee Young”
“PR Joa Kim Hee Young”
let's go.
我们走吧。
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Go let off some steam.
去发泄一下情绪吧
Smoke billowed from her head.
烟雾从她的头上冒出来。
Where?
在哪里？
Hey, wait a minute.
嘿，等等。
anything.
任何事物。
Hey, up there.
嘿，在上面。
die.
死。
- Hey, don't kill the hostages. - What?
- 嘿，别杀人质 - 什么？
Don't kill the hostages.
不要杀害人质。
- Shoot - Death.
- 射击 - 死亡。
die.
死。
Oops, why aren't you dead yet?
哎呀，怎么还没死呢？
That
那
are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
I haven't played for a long time, let's go.
好久没玩了，走吧。
OK
好的。
Why do you go so far?
你为什么要做得太过分？
What?
什么？
You work too hard.
你工作太辛苦了。
You can give up halfway , but I can't.
你可以半途而废 ，但我不能。
I want to do well and be accepted.
我想做得很好并被接受。
This makes me happy and excited.
这让我感到高兴和兴奋。
Uncle, please give me some sundaes.
叔叔，请给我一些圣代。
Remove all internal organs except the liver.
取出除肝脏以外的所有内脏。
There are also fried foods and oden.
还有油炸食品和关东煮。
- Oden, can you pick up? - Can.
- 奥登，你能接起来吗？ - 可以。
Hello, please give me two glasses of lemonade.
你好，请给我两杯柠檬水。
Feels great. There's nothing better than this.
感觉真好。 没有什么比这更好的了。
Li Zhenjiang
李镇江
Stop talking about me. Are you OK?
别再谈论我了。 你好吗？
Very bad
很坏
- Are you going to give birth? - not yet.
- 你要生了吗？ - 还没有。
Despite this, the cervix is ​​still only two centimeters wide. You have to wait until you reach ten centimeters.
尽管如此，子宫颈仍然只有两厘米宽。 你必须等到你长到十厘米。
OMG.
我的天啊。
Looking for Ten Centimeters?
寻找十厘米？
Just listening to it makes you think the body has been torn into pieces.
光是听着就让人觉得 尸体已经被撕成碎片。
I want to give my body sugar. Then let’s go in first.
我想给身体补充糖分。 那么就先进去吧。
- I'll give you a call after the presentation. - Hey
- 演示结束后我会给你打电话。 - 嘿
Have a chocolate latte, give it to me, okay?
喝一杯巧克力拿铁， 给我喝，好吗？
Now I really want something sweet.
现在我真的很想吃点甜的东西。
Thanks
谢谢
sorry.
对不起。
May I? Does it hurt anywhere? or...
可以吗？ 有没有哪里疼？或者...
I'm really sorry. I will call 119...
真的很抱歉。我会拨打119...
Wait a moment. not hot. That's okay, but...
等一下。不热。 没关系，但是……
Yes
是的
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
I am really sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
I'm really sorry, but...
我真的很抱歉，但是...
I'm very anxious now.
我现在很着急。
a while.
一会儿。
here.
这里。
Please give me a call. I will find a way to compensate.
请给我打电话。我会想办法补偿的。
Hey, you shouldn't ride your bike on the sidewalk.
嘿，你不应该 在人行道上骑自行车。
I am really sorry.
我真的很抱歉。
Come on, you look busy.
走吧，你看起来很忙。
sorry.
对不起。
Yes
是的
at least be polite
至少要有礼貌
Earth communication?
地球通讯？
" Chairman Seo Dong-hoon of Earth Communications"
“地球通信徐东勋 会长”
Earth communication?
地球通讯？
that's all.
就这样。
You know this.
你知道这个。
I know, so why give it to me?
我知道，那为什么要给我？
That is...
那是...
I'm not alone...
我不是一个人...
Is it Song Sun Tae's masterpiece?
是宋善泰的杰作吧？
here.
这里。
Yes
是的
You really hope to show up as the second group. You have access to a conference room.
你好希望作为第二组出现。 您可以使用一间会议室。
Thanks
谢谢
How are you feeling today?
今天你感觉怎么样？
When I arrived I was very nervous.
当我到达时，我非常紧张。
Are you extremely nervous?
你是否极度紧张？
Yes, the work was never shown. There used to be such a big company
是的，从未展示过作品。 以前有这么大的公司
There is always a first time for everything.
凡事总有第一次。
correct?
正确的？
Lu Yu's assistant
鲁宇的助理
Hello
你好
I am Park Yoon Jo from PR Jo Ah.
我是 PR Jo Ah 的 Park Yoon Jo。
This is you...
这是你...
Oh, you're here for the auction , right?
哦，你是来拍卖的 ，对吧？
I'm sorry for what just happened.
对于刚才的事情我很抱歉。
It seems you succeeded. What a relief.
看来你成功了。 真是松了口气。
It's okay, you've apologized to me a million times.
没关系， 你已经向我道歉一百万次了。
No, please call me.
不，请打电话给我。
Let's introduce the first group, right?
我们介绍第一组，对吧？
Yes, EarthComm is waiting in conference room two.
是的， EarthComm 正在二号会议室等候。
Yes
是的
- Then let's fight - Yes
- 那我们战斗吧 - 是的
Let's go, okay?
我们走吧，好吗？
PR Joa introduced the final group. Just wait for conference room three.
公关乔阿介绍了最后一组。 就这样等候三号会议室。
Well, okay, go ahead.
嗯，好吧，继续吧。
Incidentally
顺便一提
Won't you bless me?
你不祝福我吗？
I'm going to blow them away.
我要把他们吹走。
Don't stutter or be distracted.
不要结巴或心不在焉。
this
这
You must be doing well. All Park Yoon Joo I believe in you
你一定过得很好。 全部 朴允珠 我相信你
"Marketing Team 1, Team Leader Gao Dongjun"
《营销一队， 组长高东均》
Why did the marketing department come to take a look? Bid presentations are also available here.
市场部为什么要过来看？ 此处还提供投标演示文稿。
No, not when you have to show your work. I didn't see you calling us.
不，当你必须展示自己的作品时。 我没看到你给我们打电话。
They clearly despise each other.
他们显然互相看不起对方。
- The sales department invited them to come - why?
- 销售部门邀请他们来 - 为什么？
This works for both ads. and public relations work
这适用于两个广告。 和公共关系工作
So I wanted to come back and have a look.
所以我想再过来看看。
I don't want answers.
我不想得到答案。
I hate arrogant attitudes. Are marketers alone?
我讨厌傲慢的态度。 营销人员孤身一人吗？
is that so?
是这样吗？
I hate it too.
我也讨厌它。
Is it right?
是对的吗？
We are in the strategic management department. As for them, they are doing business.
我们在战略管理部门。 至于他们，则是做生意的。
There may be more such people.
这样的人可能会更多。
But we are the heart of this company.
但我们是这家公司的核心。
This is the insect manager.
这是昆虫管理员。
Do you really need help? People are busy.
你真的需要帮助吗？ 人们很忙。
Marketing is the core of the company. We are just a PR team.
营销是公司的核心。 我们只是一个公关团队。
What would we do without you?
没有你，我们怎么办？
We must already have a marketing department.
我们必须已经有一个营销部门。
Please take a seat.
请坐。
You coward!
你这个胆小鬼！
Jaemin's assistant
宰珉的助理
Still don't want to join our team again?
仍然不想再次加入我们的团队吗？
Come on, you're just flattering reporters. then spend the money
得了吧，你们只是在奉承记者而已。 然后把钱花掉
No one ever compliments your work.
从来没有人称赞过你的工作。
Is it right?
是对的吗？
Assistant Jaemin, you are always welcome, okay?
宰民助理，我们永远欢迎你， 好吗？
Don't try to steal him away, Go Boss.
别想把他偷走，Go Boss。
Oh, I'm so scared.
哦，我好害怕。
Please give me a call.
请给我打电话。
here.
这里。
We think about strategy...
我们思考策略...
Promotion and Management Offline and Online
推广与管理 离线和在线
Promotion Goal Offline is...
促销目标 离线是...
Yuncheng
云城
Sit down for a while.
坐下来一会儿。
Mr. President, what's wrong?
总统先生，怎么了？
"Celtics Online and Offline Activities Hello Hope"
《凯尔特人队线上线下活动 Hello Hope》
We focus on communication.
我们注重沟通。
The target is people over 30, not people in their 20s or teens.
目标是30岁以上的人， 而不是20多岁或十几岁的人。
Let's see why.
让我们看看原因。
This is a bacterium called Lactobacillus plantarum
这是一种细菌，名叫 植物乳杆菌
Lactic acid bacteria are known to prevent wrinkles and increase moisture.
众所周知，乳酸菌 防止皱纹并增加水分。
Lactobacillus plantarum is one of the most common foods around us.
植物乳杆菌 是我们周围最常见的食物之一。
That's kimchi.
那是泡菜。
We expect people in their 30s
我们预计 30 多岁的人
This is our target customer group
这是我们的目标客户群
Will be most interested in these cosmetics
会对这些化妆品最感兴趣
If there are no questions, my speech will end here.
如果没有问题的话 我的演讲到这里就结束了。
Thanks
谢谢
Yuncheng
云城
We are just supporting actors.
我们只是配角。
This auction...
本次拍卖...
They have chosen EarthComm.
他们已经选择了 EarthComm。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
So what should we do?
那么我们应该做什么呢？
What else can I do? We have to get it right.
我还可以做些什么？我们必须把它做好。
We must do well.
我们必须做得好。
But you said he has chosen EarthComm.
但你说 他已经选择了EarthComm。
We rarely show work. with the big companies here
我们很少展示作品。 与这里的大公司
let's do it.
我们开始做吧。
Even if you are just looking for experience. Let's give it a try, shall we?
即使您只是在寻找经验。 我们来尝试一下，好吗？
I have to go.
我得走了。
- Yes, this is true.
- 是的， 这是真的。
Anyway, I have chosen. I don't have to stay, right?
反正我已经选择了。 我不必留下来，对吧？
Of course, don't worry. I'll handle it myself.
当然，不用担心。 我自己会处理的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。
Progressing well.
进展顺利。
Damn, Earthcomm certainly lives up to the hype.
该死， Earthcomm 确实不负众望。
Assistant Jiemin, please help me.
杰珉助理，请帮帮我。
Yes
是的
Your presentation is impressive.
你的演讲令人印象深刻。
Damn, you introduced it so well.
妈的，你介绍得真好。
- I praise it so much - You don’t have to look at other companies’ profiles
- 我太称赞它了 - 你不用看其他公司的介绍
- Congratulations - Thank you very much
-恭喜 你 -非常感谢
Thanks
谢谢
Please take good care of yourself.
请好好照顾自己。
Well done.
做得太好了。
I performed well today.
今天我表现得很好。
Won't you bless me?
你不祝福我吗？
You must be doing well. All Park Yoon Joo I believe in you
你一定过得很好。 全部 朴允珠 我相信你
he already knows
他已经知道了
"The characters, events, organizations, and backgrounds in the play are all fictitious."
“剧中的人物、事件、组织、背景都是虚构的。”
Narrated by Thicha Leelawongpanich
Thicha Leelawongpanich 旁白